<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2021 Ad5001 -->
<application>
    <id>eu.ad5001.LogarithmPlotter</id>
    <id type="desktop">eu.ad5001.LogarithmPlotter.desktop</id>
    <launchable type="desktop-id">logarithmplotter.desktop</launchable>
    <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
    <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
    
    <name>LogarithmPlotter</name>
    <name xml:lang="fr">LogarithmPlotter</name>
    <icon type="remote">http://apps.ad5001.eu/icons/apps/logarithmplotter.svg</icon>
    <summary>2D plotter software to make BODE plots, sequences and repartition functions</summary>
    <summary xml:lang="fr">Logiciel de traçage 2D pour les diagrammes de BODE, les suites et les fonctions de répartition</summary>
    <description>
        <p>
            LogarithmPlotter is, as it's name suggests, a plotter made with logarithm scales in mind. With an object system similar to Geogebra's, it allows dynamic creation of plots with very few limitations.
        </p>
        <p>
            It's primary use is to quickly create asymptotic Bode Diagrams, but it's extensible nature and ability to switch to non-logarithmic scales allow it to create other things with it, like sequences or statistical repartition functions.
        </p>
    </description>
    <description xml:lang="fr">
        <p>
            LogarithmPlotter est, comme son nom l'indique, un créateur de graphes et diagrammes 2D réalisé avec l'échelle logarithmique en tête. Avec un système d'objets similaire à Geogebra, ce qui lui permet de créer des graphes avec peu de limitations.    
        </p>
        <p>
            Son intérêt principal est de permettre de créer des diagrammes asymptotiques de Bode, mais sa nature extensible et sa capacité à passer à une échelle non-logarithmique lui permet de créer d'autres choses.
        </p>
    </description>
    
    <categories>
        <category>Network</category>
        <category>Feed</category>
    </categories>
    <url type="homepage">https://apps.ad5001.eu/logarithmplotter/</url>
    <url type="bugtracker">https://git.ad5001.eu/Ad5001/LogarithmPlotter/issues/</url>
    <url type="help">https://git.ad5001.eu/Ad5001/LogarithmPlotter/wiki/</url>
    <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">http://apps.ad5001.eu/img/full/logarithmplotter.png</screenshot>
    </screenshots>
    <releases>
        <release version="0.0.1" date="2021-07-15"/>
    </releases>
      <content_rating type="oars-1.0">
    </content_rating>
    <update_contact>mail@ad5001.eu</update_contact>
</application>


